http://www.augustinians.org.au/home/site-items/privacy-policy/

OSA : Privacy Policy
Skip to navigation
Skip to content
Login
Search:
Child Safety FirstApologyChild Protection PolicyOptions for RedressSupport ServicesPrior General’s letter on Child ProtectionPastoral Outreach ForumAugustineAugustine's motherSpirituality of St AugustineThe Rule of St AugustineWritings of St AugustineHis relevance for youthAugustine & Monica feast daysOSAWho are the Augustinians?Our Mission StatementInternational OSA historyOSA in Australia todayOSA History AustraliaOSA in KoreaBecoming an AugustinianNews & EventsOSA News AustraliaOSA Events AustraliaOSA News InternationalMinistriesMinistry ProfilesAdditional informationGalleriesProvince of CebuOrganisationsFriends of St AugustineAugustinian Formation Association (AFA)Augustinian Volunteers AustraliaAustralian Filipino Augustinian SolidarityOSA international youth encountersAsia Pacific Augustinian ConferenceAugustinian NGO at the United Nations
/Home/Site Items/Privacy Policy (en515)
Privacy Policy
This website respects your privacy. It neither gathers nor shares with others any personal information about its users.
This website www.osa.org.au will not sell, trade, rent, share or disclose your e-mail address or other submitted personal information with any other person or groups without your expressed permission (unless required to do so by law or by a court order).
We are a non-commercial, not for profit website. We do not promote or endorse any products, intellectual property, etc.  Osa.org.au will not send or cause to be sent to your e-mail address any commercial advertising.
If you contact this website and the nature of your communication calls for a response, we will or may send you e-mail pertaining to the subject of your communication.
This Privacy Policy applies only to information collected by this website. This website contains links to other sites; www.osa.org.au is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites.
We encourage our users to read the privacy statements of each and every website that seeks or collects personally identifiable information.
Parents should advise children and teenagers to check for a privacy policy on any web site that asks them for any information about themselves, and to check with a parent or teacher before transmitting any information.
Site MapPrivacy Policy
© 2013 Augustinians Australia. All rights reserved.
Site MapPrivacy Policy
back to top
